孩子们 2007年的春天 我和罗宾之间的关系发展得很顺利
Kids, in the spring of 2007, everything was great between me and Robin.
所以我们想要进一步发展
So we decided to try and make it even better.
我们决定同居
We decided to move in together.
我打算叫搬家公司的车明早8点到
So, I can have the moving truck here by 8:00 am.
大家觉得怎么样?
Does that sound good to everybody?
顺便问一下 泰德走后 他的屋子怎么处理?
By the way, what are you guys doing with Ted's room?
如果你们需要分担房租的话 我愿跟你们合租...
'Cause if you need help with the rent, I'll take it.
你为什么想跟我们住在一起
Why would you want to live with us?
我才不认为你们 那个样子就叫"生活"
I don't call what you guys do "living."
这么说吧 我需要一间 离这个酒吧较近的房子
Here's the deal, I need a room closer to the bar.
从酒吧带个女孩回我的公寓
It takes me exactly 23 minutes
要花上整整23分钟
to get a girl from the bar back to my apartment.
而在这漫长的23分钟里会发生很多事情
A lot can go wrong in 23 minutes.
一切都将非常的热辣
This is going to be so hot.
她来付钱
She's paying.
我发誓  如果他不给我回电话
I swear, if he doesn't call me back,
我就要这么做了
I'm going to go through with this.
快点 司机
Please hurry, sir.
咱们来点刺激的
I want to do dirty stuff with you.
这事他想都别想
Stuff I won't let him do.
闯一个红灯多加二十的车费
Every red light run is an extra $20.
亲爱的?
Baby?
不不不  都是我的错
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. It was all my fault.
我醉了
I am so drunk.
我一醉就会发狂
When I'm this drunk, I go crazy!
我相信你会的
I bet you do.
看着啊
Check this out.
出什么事了 我的纽约警察?
What up NYPD?
这么近?
So close.
明白了吧?如果我在这儿住 那我直接带她上楼就行了
See? If I had a room here all I have to do is get them upstairs.
合租吧 大家都会过得很愉快的
Come on, guys. It'll be great!
我们会在你们睡着了以后进去
We'll come in after you guys are asleep
并在你们起床之前离开
and I'll be gone before you wake up.
也就是说 你们做完事后 到早晨让我们喊那讨厌的女孩起床
So, you get to have sex and we get to wake some skanky girl up in the morning
然后把她轰走?
and kick her out?
拜托 莉莉
God, Lily.
我当然会告诉她 我的确爱上过她之后假装上厕所
Some guy just told her that he loved her then pretended to go to the bathroom
之后就不会再露面了 你就不能给她沏杯咖啡?
and never came back you can't make her a cup of coffee?
真不错
Real nice.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
Transcript : Raceman Subtitles : Willow's Team
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第十八集
翻译：    唐伯虎点雷管        校对：     Alice
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
你所有的厚夹克都 放在标着"冬季"的箱子里面了
I put all your heavy jackets in this box marked "winter."
所有的花色毛衣都在 标着"比利・克斯比"的箱子里
And all your colorful sweaters in this box marked "Bill Cosby."
真有意思 不过美国人 还是挺喜欢比利・克斯比这小子
Make fun, but America loved that guy for a reason.
Wow!
快完了
Almost done.
还没呢
Not so fast.
拿着你的剑
Take your sword.
Wow.
- 一个时代结束了 - 是啊
- End of an era. - Yeah.
把这两把剑分开是有点无奈 但是你需要这把剑
It's a bummer to break up the set, but you're going to need that sword.
没错 我住的地方有好多坏人
It's true-- my building is infested with dragons.
我们的大男孩终于要搬走了
Looks like our little boy is finally moving out.
就像他昨天还是个可爱的小家伙
It seems like just yesterday he was a cute little freshmen.
时而跳瑞格舞 时而玩极限飞盘
Discovering Reggae and ultimate Frisbee.
他这一步比别人迈出得晚 但我们从未催过他
He did it later than the other kids but we never pushed him.
因为我们知道 总有一天他会迈出这一步的
We knew he'd get there.
你们还没有搬到一起 对吧?
You haven't moved in yet, have you?
你们需要做一下这个测试
Good. You guys have to take this quiz.
我在一本杂志上找到的
I found it in a magazine.
题为"你们准备好同居了?"
It's called the "Are you ready to move in together?" quiz.
如果是"你们穿内裤吗"诸如此类的问题
Well, if it's anything like you're "Are you wearing panties" quiz,
我退出
I'm out.
第一题
Question one,
泰德 你想搬去和罗宾住?
Ted, "Do you want to move in with Robin?"
想
Mm. Yes.
你第一题就错了
Oh, you got the first one wrong.
答案应该是"不" 事实上你想单身
The answer is "no," you secretly want to be single
并且和你的好友巴尼在一起
and hang out with your awesome friend Barney."
第二题
Question two.
你觉得你还能找到比泰德更棒的男孩?
Robin, "Do you think you can score a hotter guy than Ted?"
正确 答案就是尴尬的沉默
Correct. The answer was awkward silence.
第三题 我编了这个 测试是为了证明一个问题吗?
Question three, "Did I just make up this quiz to prove a point?"
是的
Yes.
Yes, I did.
真的吗?你是说测试题 不是从《老黄页杂志》上抄来的?
Really? You mean it's not from Old Yellow Legal Pad Magazine?
那么 我们都同意啦?
So? We all agree?
我们把泰德的东西搬回来吧?
We move Ted's stuff back up here?
我不同意 我们还是想住到一起
Mm... no. We're still moving in together.
为什么?简直疯了
Why? This is crazy.
你不要命啦?那女人...
Ted you're throwing your life away. This girl is blinding you.
用她亮丽的头发 容易让人迷失的乳房蒙蔽了你
With her shiny hair and her boobed shaped boobs.
这对你来说 也没什么好处 你知道的...
This is bad for you, too, you know.
当他看到没化妆的你 你会有什么感觉?
How are you going to feel when he sees you without any makeup?
我现在就没化妆
I'm not wearing makeup right now.
上帝啊 你真漂亮
Holy crap, you're beautiful.
当你不能再偶尔偷偷地 吸烟的时候你有什么感觉?
All right then, how will you feel when you can't sneak the occasional cigarette?
拜托 罗宾不吸烟
Oh, come on, Robin doesn't smoke.
等等 你吸烟?
Wait, do you?
当然不 为什么这么问?
Of course not. Why?
不要告诉我该怎样生活!
Don't tell me how to live my life!
泰德 我不能让你这么做
Ted, I can't let you do this.
拜托 现在已经进行中了
Come on. This is happening.
与其在那争论 为什么不帮帮我?
So instead of fighting it why, why don't you just help?
- 你希望我帮你? - 是啊
- You want me to help you? - Yeah.
好吧  泰德
Okay, Ted.
我来帮你
I'll help you.
真不敢相信 他帮我们搬了一箱东西下去
Can't believe we actually got him to take a box down.
也许他最终会上路的
Maybe he's finally getting on board.
卡车呢?
Where's the truck?
巴尼呢?
Where's Barney?
等车呢
Wait for it.
简直难以相信 除了这一整箱的锅盖
I can't believe this! Everything I own in the world is in there.
我所有的一切都在那卡车上了
Except for this box of pot lids.
还有这把剑
And the sword.
我要杀了他 我向上帝保证我要杀了他
I'm going to kill him. I swear to God I'm going to kill him!
这把剑现在还是让我给你保管
Right. Maybe I'll just hold on to that. For now.
马修  这儿只有我们俩了
Marshall, we live alone.
这太爽了!
This is so great!
现在我们终于可以自由地 过我们梦想已久的二人世界了
We can finally do all the things we always said we wanted to do if we lived alone.
我知道我开始想做什么了
Oh, I know what I want to start with.
我们开始了 是吗？
So, here we are, right?
赤裸裸的坐在公寓里
Sitting around the apartment naked.
- 棒极了 - 是啊
- Awesome. - Yep.
看来没有我想象中的那么棒
It's not as awesome as I thought it would be.
- 我屁股痒 - 我冷了
- My butt itches. - I'm cold.
我也发现了
I noticed.
好像你就是一个聊天的对象
Yeah, like you're one to talk, Pointy.
我不知道你有没有看见我那47条短信
Barney, I don't know if you got my other 47 messages,
如果我的东西在一小时内 还没有出现 我就要报警了
but if my stuff isn't here within the hour I'm calling the cops.
这是我最后一次打电话给你
This is the last time I'm calling you.
因为我的充电器也在那卡车上
Because my charger's in the back of the truck.
别担心 巴尼 他会把东西送来的
Don't worry, it's Barney. He'll bring the stuff back.
知道吗?我希望真正地搬进来
No, it's just... I was really looking forward to settling in, you know?
希望已经放好电视
Maybe setting up my TV.
躺在床上看电影
Watching a movie in bed.
怎么了?
What?
真的要在卧室里放台电视?
Do we really want a TV in the bedroom?
我想是这样的
I thought we did.
我可不想这样
I'm not sure that we do.
那好 你说电视放哪儿?
Well, where else would we put my TV?
我们可以把它放在地下室的储藏室里
We could just put it in our storage unit in the basement.
要是我们想看电视怎么办?
But wouldn't we miss my TV?
- 会吗? - 会
- Would we? - Yes, we would.
那台电视陪伴我们很多年了
We've had that TV for a long time
如果放在卧室的话 会更有家的感觉
and we would feel more at home if it were setup in our bedroom.
- 我们需要喝点酒 不是吗? - 看来是的
- We need wine, don't we? - Yes, we do.
我们要不要到卧室去?
Should we, um, move this to the bedroom?
为什么?
Why?
泰德已经搬走了
Ted doesn't live here anymore.
我们可以在任何地方做这件事
We can do it wherever we want.
还有件事你知道吗?
You know what else?
我们再也不需要保持安静了
We don't have to be quiet anymore.
想多大声就多大声
We can be as loud as we want.
我认为我们需要制订一些基本规则
Okay, I think we need to lay down some ground rules.
我们不需要保持安静 但是不意味着必须出声
Just because we can be loud doesn't mean we have to be loud.
即使这会使你兴奋
And although it might turn you on,
你尖叫着"我是最棒的" 这个对我并不起作用
you screaming, "I'm the best," doesn't do much for me.
这比一直大喊"泰德搬走了"好多了
Well, it's a lot better than yelling, "Ted's not here," over and over again.
至少我说的是实话
Well, at least what I said is true.
那不是必需的
Well, that was unnecessary.
虽然我只有这一箱东西了 我想我还是可以打开它
Well, since I only have one box I figure I might as well unpack it.
你说这些东西该放哪儿?
Mm, where do you think we should put it?
我认为可以放在橱柜里 除非你有个专门用来放锅盖的房间
Well, unless you have a separate pot lid room, I was thinking the cupboard.
怎么了?
What?
关键是我的厨房有点小
Uh, the thing is my kitchen is kind of small.
还有我已经有很多锅盖了
And, um, I already have a bunch of pot lids
而且是带着锅的  所以...
and mine come with pots, so...
你的意思是不可能为我 劳神费力搬进来的
You're saying there's no way to make room for the single box of stuff
这点儿东西腾地方了?
I try to move into our place?
你为什么不把他们放到...
Well, why don't you just take it down to the...
不要说储藏室
Do not say storage space.
我想说的是垃圾箱
I was going to say Dumpster.
这箱东西是我在这世界上 唯一财产了
Damn it, Robin, this is all I have left in the world--
八个锅盖和一把剑
eight pot lids and a sword.
是啊 关于那把剑...
Yeah, about the sword.
喂?
Hello.
莫斯比先生 穿上西服
Put on the suit, Mr. Mosby.
巴尼 我知道是你 我的东西呢?
Barney, I know it's you. Where's my stuff?
不是我
It's not me.
如果你还想见到你的宝贝
If you want to see your precious possessions again,
穿上那件西服
put on the suit.
哪件?
What suit?
什么在响?门铃?
Ding-dong. Oh, what's that? The doorbell.
我说的就是那件西服
That's the suit I'm talking about.
我还没有走到门那儿呢
I haven't gotten to the door yet.
好吧 到门那了说一声
Oh, okay, let me know when you get there.
好 我打开门了 确实有一件西服
Okay, I opened it. And there's a suit there.
那就是我说的西服
That's the suit I'm talking about.
- 巴尼... - 我不是巴尼
- Barney.... - This isn't Barney.
但我听说那家伙挺出色的
But I hear that guy's awesome.
好吧  听好了
All right. Listen very carefully.
如果你能完成一系列的挑战 你就可以拿到你的那些东西了
You will get your stuff back if you are able to complete a series of challenges.
任务一 穿上西服
Number one, put on the suit.
任务二  一小时内到麦克莱儿酒吧见我
Number two, meet me at McClaren's in an hour.
我们都没有见过面 我怎么知道哪个是你?
How will I know who to look for since we've never met?
我长得像巴尼
I look like Barney.
泰德 你好啊
Oh, hey, Ted.
西装配运动鞋
Suit and sneakers.
有点像艾伦・德杰尼勒斯的风格 (艾伦・德杰尼勒斯 Showtime1982年度"全美最滑稽的人")
A little Ellen DeGeneres but you pull it off.
我没有别的鞋子了  因为你偷走了它们
I don't have any other shoes because you stole them along
还有我的其他财产
with everything else I own in the world.
巴尼 卡车在哪?
Where's the truck, Barney?
巴尼
Barney.
并未被我勒索卡车的那人在叫我巴尼
People's whose trucks I'm not holding for ransom call me Barney.
我想你该叫我将军
I think you should call me The Commodore.
-我是不会那样叫你的... -那你就拿不到你的东西了
- I'm not calling you... - You're not getting your stuff back.
我可以拿回我的东西?
Can I please have my stuff back...
将军...
The Commodore?
不行
No.
情况是这样的 泰德 咱们是哥们
Here's the deal, Ted, you're my bro.
而你即将变成怕老婆的 令人沮丧的  没有尊严的小男人
And you're about to become a henpecked, beaten down, shell of a man.
所以今晚是咱哥俩 最后一次这么开心的聚会
So tonight, we are going to have one last awesome night together as bros.
这是个兄弟散伙会
It's a bro-ing away party.
是个非常特别的时刻
A special bro-casion.
是兄弟抉择的聚会
A bro-choice rally.
是阿波罗上的兄弟们大喜的日子
Bro-time at the Apollo.
我的兄弟
Oh, bro me.
好吧 我该做什么?
Well, so what do I have to do?
错 不是你该做什么 而是你想做什么?
No, it's not what you have to do, it's what you want to do,
你想在回去之前
and you want to have a good time
度过一个美好的时光
before you go take Fun Ted out back and shoot him.
那么... 第一件事应该是...
So... first thing on the docket...
- 去把那个女孩的电话搞来 - 不 绝不
- get me that girl's number. - Absolutely not.
太糟了
Mm. That's too bad.
这样吧 我们设想一下 如果我是你的那些东西
Hey, hypothetical question: if I was all your stuff,
我是想待在东河的底部 还是哈德逊河的底部
would I rather be at the bottom of the East River or The Hudson?
快看 世界级大力士
Hey, look, world's strongest man is on.
是卢・费雷格诺用牙齿把汽车
Ooh, it's the one where Lou Ferrigno pulls the bus
从帕却吉家拖走的那段
from the Partridge family with his teeth.
是最精彩的部分 泰德 快来看
It's the best one. Hey, Ted, get in...
- 就我们俩个 - 恩
- We live alone. - Yay.
我赢了
Well, I win.
你必须把你的 电话号码告诉我朋友
You need to give my friend your phone number.
我真的没想到卢・费雷格诺 可以拖动那辆汽车
Wow, I really didn't think Lou Ferrigno could pull that bus.
你确定这是直播? 看上去画面有点老
Are you sure this is live? It looks pretty old.
是直播  看上去老 是因为电视有些年头了
Yeah, that's 'cause the, uh, TV is old.
那... 我明天可以打电话给你？
So, I'll, uh, call you tomorrow?
可以 不过不要太早 我要去做礼拜
Yeah. Um, not too early. I have church.
兄弟 你很有魅力啊
You were impressive, buddy.
干得不错 好吧 我们开始下一个挑战
Nice work. All right, next challenge.
行啦　不要再挑战了 听着 这是我和罗宾同居的第一夜
No. No next challenge. Look, this is my first night living with Robin.
她可能正为我 在这儿跟你鬼混生气
She's probably pissed I'm spending it out with you.
小朋友  也许今晚 就是我们最后在一起了
This might be our last hurrah, my little friend.
今天我要给你做一顿 你从来没有享受过的超级晚餐
Marshall, I am gonna cook you the best dinner of your life.
你喜不喜欢吃...
How would you like a...
带番茄酱和保鲜膜的鸡蛋卷？
one-egg omelet with some ketchup and film?
我猜平时都是泰德去买东西
Guess Ted's the one who did the shopping.
重大发现 速食比萨
Ooh, look, a microwave pizza!
估计微波炉也是泰德的
Guess the microwave was Ted's, too.
是啊
Yeah.
连浴巾都是他的
So were all the towels.
终于发现在这个公寓里所有 有用的东西都是泰德的
Turns out that everything that was useful in this apartment was Ted's.
所有那些过时的令人啼笑皆非的海报 都是我在大学的时候买的
Everything that was a Foghat poster we bought ironically in college was mine.
马修
Marshall.
怎么了 亲爱的
Yeah, baby?
我想泰德了
I miss Ted.
刚分别就给他打电话是不是太快了？
Is it too soon to call him?
不  我们不能打
No, we shouldn't.
这可是他和罗宾的第一夜啊 我不想打扰他们
I don't want to interrupt his first night living with Robin.
好枪法
Ha, nice shooting.
如果我们再赢一局就可以在 银河系快餐店吃到免费的洋葱圈了
You know, if we win this one it's free onion rings at the Intergalactic Snack Shack.
不错啊
What a bargain.
只要每局游戏交20元钱
We only had to spend 20 bucks a game.
认栽吧　你玩得多愉快啊
Admit it, you're having fun.
也许吧
Maybe.
我觉得那小女孩 掉进那大桶里时挺好玩
I mean, it was pretty funny when that little girl fell over that space barrel.
好样的 我们赢了
Nice... We win.
灰溜溜的走了 游戏输了 怎么了?
Oh, walk of shame, walk of game-- what up?
再来一局?
Okay. Let's go one more.
- 算了吧 - 我知道你想玩
- I don't know. - You know you want to.
好吧 再来一盘 我要先给罗宾打个电话
All right, let's do it-- I just got to call Robin real quick.
这就是以后会发生的事情
Oh, so that's what it's gonna be like from now on?
算了 你给你的老女人打吧 去请求她的允许吧
No. Okay, okay. You call your old lady and ask permission to have fun.
至于我  我要去 吃我们的战利品洋葱圈了
Me, I will be at the Snack Shack eating our victory onion rings Han style.
Han Solo 星球大战的男主
我自己去了
Solo.
- 嗨　泰德 - 嗨　亲爱的 听我说
- Hey, Ted. - Hey, sweetie listen,
真不好意思  我很晚才能回去 别等我了
I'm really sorry but I'm gonna be pretty late, so don't wait up.
没事  继续忙你的就是了
Oh, it's totally fine. You do what you got to do.
你真是太善解人意了 我爱你
Thanks. You're the best. I love you.
我也爱你 再见
I love you, too. Bye.
不好意思久等了
Hey, sorry about that. Thanks for holding.
如果您能把《枪与军火》的定金退还给我
Um, so if you could go ahead and cancel my subscription to Guns and Ammo,
我将很感激
that would be great.
不不 这本杂志挺好的 真的
No, it's a great magazine. Really great.
他们还登了我的三封信
They've printed three of my letters.
只是因为我男朋友要搬来和我住
It's just that my boyfriend is moving in
他不喜欢跟武器有关的东西
and he kind of doesn't approve of the whole gun thing.
一个免费的手榴弹电话?
A free hand grenade phone?
这样吧  我给你我工作的地址
You know what? Let me give you my work address.
我搞定了 亲爱的!
I did it, baby!
我买了啤酒 还有食物
I got beer. I got food.
我们再也不需要泰德了
We don't need Ted anymore.
我现在是这个公寓的供应商了
I am the provider of this apartment now,
而且我已经开始供应了
and I have provided!
"P-r-o-v-o-d-e"? Provided (马修在考虑动词的不同时态)
"Provode"? Provided.
总之  我买了我们需要的一切
Anyway, I got us everything we need.
你能把卫生纸递给我?
Could you toss me the toilet paper?
亲爱的再等会儿啊 我马上回来
Be right back, baby. Sit tight.
我得承认 原来我不认为... 但是
Hey, I got to admit, um... I didn't think I would, but, uh...
今晚我的确过得很愉快
I had a really good time tonight.
你真够朋友 巴尼
You're a good friend, Barney.
那兄弟 你何不...
Hey, man, why don't you, uh...
何不告诉我我的卡车在哪?
why don't you tell me where my truck is.
我可不这么认为
No, I don't think so.
你把我的卡车弄哪去了?!
Where's my truck?!
你知道我为什么 没有把你的东西还给你?
Do you know why I haven't given you any of your possessions back yet?
因为你是英国皇家海军的杰克上将?
Uh, because you're Admiral Jerk of the British Royal Douchery?
因为你不想要它们
Because you don't want them back.
你本来随时可以离开 但是 泰德你没有
You could've left at any time tonight, but you didn't, Ted.
为什么会这样?
Why is that?
因为我不想空着手回罗宾那儿
Because I didn't want to go back to Robin's without my stuff.
错  你知道我怎么想的?
False. You know what I think?
你和她整天腻在一起 感觉不爽
I think you spent one day with her and it already sucked.
你不想去那 她也不想你待在那
I think you didn't like being there, she didn't like having you there
你们俩同时都意识到这是个巨的错误
and you both realized that you made a huge mistake.
这就是为什么你和罗宾同居的第一夜
And that's why you spent your first night living with Robin
你却在外面陪我玩激光射击
out playing laser tag with me.
这也是为什么三秒钟前
And that's why three seconds ago
你没有说 我家 我们的家 或者 家
you didn't call it "my place" or "our place" or "home,"
而是说 罗宾那儿
you called it "Robin's."
你知道我想说什么吗?
You know what?
你可以拿着我的东西
You can keep my stuff.
怎么样?东西找到了吗?
- Hey. - Hey, did you get the truck back?
没有
No.
为什么没拿回来啊 怎么回事?
Why not? What happened?
他把我惹恼了 所以我回来了
Oh, he pissed me off so much, I left.
我只想回来 安安静静地看部电影
Anyway, I just wanted to come back here, space out and watch a movie.
有没有不是吴宇森导演的电影啊?
Do you anything that wasn't made by John Woo?
为什么 你有?
Why, do you?
不看电影了 我坐下来休息下吧
You know, forget the movie. I just want to sit.
怎么了?
What?
也没啥  只是我 在这张桌子上吃饭
It's just I eat at that table.
那好 我把鞋脱了
Fine, I'll take my shoes off.
你为什么不连同把我一起丢尽储藏室?
You know, why don't you just throw me down in the storage space
看来那儿是这里唯一可以容我的地方
where you have room for me.
- 泰德 别这样 - 不 是你要这样的
- Ted, come on. - No, you come on.
我今晚一晚上都对巴尼唯命是从
I had to jump through hoops all night for Barney
然后我花了一个小时才回到这儿
and then it took me an hour to get home because his place
因为他家离酒吧太远了
is so far away from the bar.
- 上帝啊 - 怎么了?
- Oh, my God. - What?
我知道巴尼把我的卡车藏哪了
I know where Barney put my truck.
回我住的地方去吧
Let's go back to my place.
我想我家更近些
I bet you my place is closer.
到了
Here we are.
你住在酒吧后的装货月台上吗?
You live in the loading dock behind the bar?
当然不是　亲爱的 这只是我的坐骑
I don't live here, baby. This is just my ride.
不成不成不成 我可不进任何带篷货车
No, no, no, no. I'm not getting into any van,
我看过《沉默的羔羊》
I've seen Silence of the Lambs.
我们在移动的后备箱里喝着香槟
Oh, my God. We're drinking champagne in the back of a moving van.
这有什么　萨拉 就是这样
Why, yes, Sara. Yes, we are.
那些说你不够活跃的火箭都是疯子
Those other Rockettes who called you slow are crazy.
我就知道  你绑架我
Oh, my God. I knew it. You're kidnapping me.
-　救命 救命 -　不 我没有
- Help! Help! - No, no, no, no.
听我解释
I can explain.
喂?
Hello?
享受旅途的快乐
Enjoying the ride?
泰德?泰德 让我们出去 快让我们出去
Ted? Ted, you let us out of here. You let us out of here this instant!
我不是泰德
This isn't Ted.
但我听说那个家伙很出色
But I hear that guy's awesome.
最后我把萨拉送回了家 把巴尼丢在了离他公寓很近的酒吧那
So I took Sara home and I took Barney to a bar near his apartment.
显然　他还从来没用那个策略
Apparently, that strategy had never occurred to him.
那个可怜的女孩肯定很困惑
That poor girl must've been so confused.
是啊
Yeah.
至少巴尼得到了深刻的教训
Well, at least Barney learned a valuable lesson.
想必你是不会愿意被人戳你痛处
You do not want to get scissor kicked in the groin by a Rockette.
我们是不是该开始搬家了?
So, uh, I guess we should get you unpacked.
是的
Yeah.
我认为该搬了
Yeah, I guess we should.
在亚马逊雨林的深处
Lily... deep within the Amazonian rainforest,
有一种树 他们只能围绕一棵大树成长
there is a type of tree that only grows around the body of an existing tree.
没有那棵树  它就活不了
It cannot survive without this tree.
它被那棵树
It is supported...
支撑着 养育着
by this tree.
我们就是那种树
Lily, we are that tree.
-　是里面那颗还是外面那颗 -　外面的
- The inside tree or the outside tree? - The outside tree.
- 不是应该有三棵吗? - 不 我和你是一棵树
- Shouldn't there be three trees? - You and I are one tree.
重点是我们是围绕着泰德存活的
Okay, look, Lily, the point is that we grew around Ted
没有他 我们就会慢慢地死去
and without him, we're slowly dying.
我们该怎么做?
What do we do?
我认为我们是要结婚
I think we can marry each other.
但同时要和泰德住在一起
But we also have to marry Ted.
我现在就可以肯定地告诉你 我父亲是不会为这样的婚礼付钱的
I'll tell you right now, my Dad is not gonna pay for that wedding.
泰德!
Ted!
你来这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
罗宾和我不打算同居了
Robin and I aren't gonna move in together after all.
怎么啦?
What happened?
我原来认为我们已经准备好了
I thought we decided we were ready?
我也觉得
I know.
我们怎么得出的那个结论?
How did we come to that again?
我不记得了  我们吵架了?
I don't remember. We were fighting?
- 这个越来越模糊了 - 是啊
- It's all so blurry. - Yeah.
有种说法同居让性生活更美好
The "let's move in together" sex was pretty amazing.
我知道
I know.
我做那事时没用手 通常是要两手齐上的
I did that thing with no hands I normally need both to do.
你知道吗? 跟你在一起很开心
You know... I'm really happy with you.
在一起很开心 这才是最重要的
I really happy with you. The way things are.
也许我们不该因为那个搅乱了生活
Maybe we shouldn't mess with that.
我也觉得不应该那样
I don't know that we should.
知道吗?我听说 不同居性生活会更美好
Hey... I hear the "let's not move in together" sex is pretty incredible.
还是回我那去吧
Let's go back to my place.
- 谢谢 - 不用谢
- Ooh, thank you. - You're welcome.
- 不 谢谢 - 你会很开心的
- No, thank you. - You'll be very happy.
我知道你们很想独享二人世界
Look, I know you guys are really excited about having the place to yourself.
直到婚后 我想说 如果不是很勉强的话...
Until after the wedding, I mean, if it's not too much of an imposition...
上帝啊 这感觉真是太棒了
God, this feels so right.
永远不要离开我们了
Never leave us again.
伙计们 罗宾还在卡车上 那还有很多的箱子
Guys, Robin's down in the truck and there's actually a lot of boxes,
也许我们应该...
so maybe we should...
我们有时间做这个?
Do we have time for this?
女士们先生们 我手里有份"十佳名字"清单
Ladies and gentlemen, I have in my hand a copy of tonight's Top Ten list.
分别是我卡车的最棒的十个名字...
The category: top ten things I would've called my truck...
那永远都不是你的卡车
It was never your truck.
如果泰德没有犯混 把它还回去的话
...if Ted hadn't been a jerk and given it back.
那是租的
It was a rental.
第十位　"The Winne-Bango."
Number ten, "The Winne-Bango."
第九位　"The Pick-Up Truck."
Number nine, "The Pick-Up Truck."
第八位　"The Ford Explore Her."
Number eight, "The Ford Explore Her."
第七位　"The You Scream Truck."
Number seven, "The You Scream Truck."
尖叫
You Scream.
第六位　"Feels On Wheels." 嗨
Number six, "Feels On Wheels." Hello!
第五位　"The Ride Her Truck."
Number five, "The Ride Her Truck."
第四位　"The 18-Squeeler."
Number four, "The 18-Squeeler."
第三位　"The Esca-Laid."
Number three, "The Esca-Laid."
第二位　"The Slam-Boney."
Number two, "The Slam-Boney."
嗯... 第一位是...
and... the number one thing I would've called my truck
如果泰德没有犯混把它还回去的话
if Ted hadn't been a jerk and given it back...
是"The '69 Chevy."
"The '69 Chevy."
不好意思
Sorry.